nestoria.co.uk 2008-04-19

# Nestoria - Privacy Policy

Welcome to Nestoria, a site owned and operated by Lokku Limited and designed to make finding a property as easy as using a search engine. 

Introduction

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy covers Lokku's treatment of personally identifiable information that Lokku collects when you are on the Nestoria site ([www.nestoria.co.uk](http://www.nestoria.co.uk/), referred to below as "this Site") and when you use Lokku's services. Please read this privacy policy carefully. By using this Site and any services we offer via this Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site. 

The policy also gives information about cookies; Lokku use of cookies; and how you may disable such cookies. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Lokku does not own or control, or to people that Lokku does not employ or manage. 

If you have any queries or comments about the policy or our use of your personal information, please get in touch with us via our feedback form. 

In general, we use the anonymous information we collect about you to: 

  * improve the features and services we offer
  * provide more personalised services to you
  * support our own marketing and promotion efforts

Cookies and tracking

Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enable us to personalise your visits to this website, simplify the signing-in procedure, keep track of your preferences and to track the usage of this website. 

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. 

Find out more about cookies [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/). 

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences). But please note that this may reduce the functionality of this Site and other websites. 

If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use Lokku services at its full potential and personalised to you. 

Like all websites, our servers automatically record 'log files' containing information about the volume and characteristics of our website traffic e.g. IP address, numbers of pages viewed, length of time spent on site. We use log files to build pictures of how our site is used that help us to monitor and improve the service. **We cannot identify you from your log files**. 

Disabling/Enabling Cookies

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled. 

Find out how to disable/enable cookies: [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)

Email a Friend

When you use the 'email a friend' feature of this Site we record which properties you have been sent to the friend solely so that we can track the popularity of those properties. We record the other details provided in the email for internal monitoring of the service. We will NOT add any information collected in this manner to our mailing lists to protect you and the recipient's privacy. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Lokku may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

Questions or Suggestions?

If you have questions or suggestions please get in touch with us via our feedback form.
